var questions = [{
  question: 'What was Han Solo frozen in?',
  choices: ['carbonite', 'ice cream', 'mollasses', 'glass'],
  answer: 'carbonite'
}, {
  question: 'On which planet did Darth Maul kill Qui-Gon Jinn?',
  choices: ['Mustafar', 'Coruscant', 'Naboo', 'Yavin'],
  answer: 'Naboo'
}, {
  question: 'Who killed Jabba the Hut?',
  choices: ['Han', 'Leia', 'Luke', 'C3P0'],
  answer: 'Leia'
}, {
  question: 'How many Death Stars did the Empire build?',
  choices: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
  answer: '2'
}, {
  question: 'Who created Star Wars?',
  choices: ['Darth Vader', 'Gene Roddenberry', 'George Lucas', 'J.R.R Tolkien'],
  answer: 'George Lucas'
}, {
  question: 'How many suns does Tatooine have?',
  choices: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
  answer: '2'
}, {
  question: 'What is the highest rank of Jedi?',
  choices: ['youngling', 'padawan', 'knight', 'master'],
  answer: 'master'
}, {
  question: 'What relation is Darth Vader to Luke Skywalker',
  choices: ['brother', 'uncle', 'father', 'nephew'],
  answer: 'father'
}, {
  question: 'What name does Obi-Wan Kenobi go by?',
  choices: ['Ben', 'Dan', 'Anakin', 'Bruce'],
  answer: 'Ben'
}, {
  question: 'What was the name of the cantina where Luke met Han Solo',
  choices: ['Bespin', 'Mos Eisley', 'Coruscant', 'Naboo'],
  answer: 'Mos Eisley'
}];
